// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What are the three states of matter?",
    answer: "solid, liquid, gas",
    options: [
      "Solid, water, vapor",
      "ice, drink indescribable stink",
      "solid, liquid, gas",
      "water"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which part of plant conducts photosynthesis?",
    answer: "Leaf",
    options: [
      "Branch",
      "Leaf",
      "Root",
      "Trunk"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "All animals need food, air, and....... to survive.",
    answer: "Water",
    options: [
      "House",
      "Shelter",
      "Fruits",
      "Water"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What do carnivore eat?",
    answer: "Meat",
    options: [
      "Meat",
      "Plants",
      "Both",
      "All of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many classes of food do we have?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  }, 
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "You should never ______ chemicals in the lab.",
      answer: "all of the above",
      options: [
      "taste",
      "touch",
      "smell",
      "all of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "What do scientist do?",
      answer: "affect the lives of humans through their scientific breakthroughs and inventions",
      options: [
      "makes",
      "do NOT repeat their investigations",
      "affect the lives of humans through their scientific breakthroughs and inventions",
      "read the steps of the investigation"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Rocks, water, air, sun and soil are ___ .",
      answer: "non-living",
      options: [
      "living",
      "non-living",
      "animals",
      "plants"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What does the term non-living mean?",
      answer: "It does not breathe, eat or drink.",
      options: [
      "It does not breathe, eat or drink.",
      "It does breathe, eat and drink.",
      "It grows.",
      "It runs."
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What shape does light travel in?",
      answer: "Waves",
      options: [
      "Waves",
      "Circles",
      "Squares",
      "Diamonds"
    ]
  },


  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];